Welcome to the games
of the 3004 Earth Olympiad,
continuing this network's tradition
of sportscasting excellence.
Celebrity Ape Fight will return
next week at its regular time.
So who should I root for?
America? Or one of those countries
I learned about at the food court?
How about those guys?
No, they're from
the Republic of French Stereotypes.
Everybody hates them.
Oh, let's go check on Hermes.
All this inspiring multiculturalism
is angrying up my blood.
Sweden?
I don't think so.
Go on, stick, touch me.
Can't do it.
Husband, you haven't been
an Olympic-class limbo-er for 20 years.
Quit lying to your pudgy self.
It does seem like Jamaica
would be able to field
a strong limbo team without you.
Yeah. Isn't that basically
all Jamaicans do?
Jamaicans have other interests.
Which is why the limbo team
got detained at the airport.
That's when they begged my husband
to step in and make an ass out of himself.
And I said I'd try my very best.
But have they seen your, you know,
physique since the old days?
I described it to them on the phone
using a series of artful euphemisms.
Don't worry, the fat pig will do fine
thanks to this flab-o-dynamic
spandex body suit I've designed.
It redistributes his weight
shifting his center of gravity
closer to his knees.
Oh, that's snug.
Those haven't descended in years.
Now that's a limbo-er's body.
Look at that fine Jamaican bacon.
Shut up, Zoidberg.
The robot bending events are starting.
Something tells me I could easily beat
those trained professionals.
Wow. That guy must be, like
the world's greatest bender.
My dreams of glory died before they began.
Welcome to my life.
Athletes, please take
your lanes for the men's 500-meter limbo.
Hermes Conrad.
Is that you inside
that dumpy little fat man?
Barbados Slim!
What are you doing here?
Last time I heard, you were in Barbados.
Yes, and I'll be going back there
with a gold medal
draped around my elegant
Caribbean shoulders.
Your body may be as perfectly sculpted
as it was 20 years ago
when you whupped my fat ass
every time we met,
but today, I feel lucky.
I see you're still able
to limbo under the bar of fashion sense.
That's it, Barbados Slim.
You've gone one toke over the line.
Limbo-ers, on your marks.
Get rubbery.
Limbo!
There they go,
and Barbados Slim takes an early lead.
God, I hope he wins.
What's this?
Hermes Conrad is closing the gap.
He's limbo'd out of retirement
and straight into my heart.
I say "Go to hell, Barbados Slim."
Go, body suit, go!
Come on, Hermes!
Beat that mahogany god!
It's Barbados, then Conrad!
Conrad pulls ahead.
And Conrad is disqualified.
Barbados Slim, my hero, takes the gold.
Ah, there, there, Hermes,
you did your best.
If I'd wanted a human Adonis
for a husband,
I'd have stayed married to Barbados Slim.
Well, enough about Hermes.
I couldn't win a medal, either,
even at bending,
the thing I was built to do.
I'm so embarrassed, I wish
everybody else was dead.
Up next,
the Fembot bending competition.
Fembots?
Methinks a clever Manbot,
suitably disguised,
might win those events,
but the charade would require
subtlety, nuance, grace.
What do you mean, I'm not registered?
My name is Coilette
and I'm from, uh, Robonia!
Coilette's a chick's name.
Yes, but Robonia sounds like something
somebody made up on the spot.
Ever been beaten up
by a guy dressed like a chick?
And it's straight!
Coilette wins!
Another gold medal for
the spunky maid from Robonia.
A perfect bend and a flawless entry.
No splash at all.
Perfect scores.
A record five gold medals for Coilette.
I'm great! Everybody else sucks!
Except that guy Bender.
He's really something.
Whoo!
All medalists
report for gender testing.
You actually thought they'd let you
walk away without an engine oil sex check?
Oh, God, I'm not going to get my medals.
They're all I have
to remember my Olympic career.
Wait! I've got it!
Professor, make a woman out of me.
Oh, I think we should just stay friends.
I don't need friends.
I need a sex change operation,
and give it to me now.
Bender, a robot sex change
is a complex and dangerous procedure.
Replacing your testosteroil
with Fembot lubricants
can cause wild mood swings
and the effects may be irreversible.
Well, let's get started.
No, you can't!
If you have even the slightest respect
for the dignity of women...
Pfft.
I'm sorry, but I must do this.
Not for you, not for Bender
but for the proud people of Robonia!
Come on, guys. Come on.
I can't watch this 'cause it's creepy
and wrong and sick.
However, I will watch out of curiosity.
Quiet! I'm about to begin the process
of reshaping Bender's body
into a tender, delicate form.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ooh! Ow! Ow!
Draining male oil.
Infusing female oil.
Removing item.
We can't wait for Coilette
any longer, damn it.
I have to go home
to watch The Zombie Osbournes.
I'm ready for my test now, boys.
Hail, hail, Robonia
A land I didn't make up.
Ooh, yeah, come on, baby. Uh.
Ooh, goodness.
Oh, yeah, baby, come on. Work your cans.
Yeah, shake it out.
I don't know which I'm more,
enraged or disgusted.
I'm just out there
making us ladies look good.
Nuh-uh. You're making us look like jerks
in front of the other genders.
But you're not really
a lady anyway, right?
Of course not.
Dear lord, a coaster.
The Femmzoil must be sashaying
girlishly into your processor.
Then change me back.
My breasts are keeping me
awake at night anyway.
Ooh!
Hello?
What? A guest spot
on Late Night with Humorbot 5.0?
I'd love to.
My own limo?
No, I don't have my own limo.
You'd better send one.
I need a rain check on
that nad swap, Professor.
I'm going on TV.
Come on, Fry, help me pick out a pantsuit.
So, Calculon,
do you want to set up this clip
from All My Circuits?
No, I think it's self-explanatory.
No!
Funny story,
the script called for me to say "Yes,"
but I gave it a little twist.
Anecdote accepted.
Snappy comeback not found.
Please put your hands together
for my next guest,
winner of five Olympic medals,
Coilette, from Robonia.
So, Coilette, many young Fembots
wish to emulate you.
Any advice for them?
Yes, Humorbot, if you ask me,
women today are too stuck up
to go out and jiggle their Jell-O
like everybody wants them to.
In fact, should I do it now?
All right, then.
Whoo! Look out, baby. Work it out.
Oh, shake that thing.
You got to use it, lady.
Shake it up a little.
That's right. Come on.
Break it out.
Madam, I am one impressed celebrity.
Oh, I bet you say that to all
the five-Olympic-gold-medal-winning
Fembots.
From this day forth, I shall
do so whenever possible.
Golly.
What?
Coilette, this may be presumptuous...
That's my favorite kind of "this."
But I would be honored
if you would join me for dinner sometime.
Whoo!
Calculon, you'd be fulfilling
this naive Robonian farm girl's fantasy.
Of course I would.
This top makes me look fat.
Is it trampy to go on a first date nude?
Yes.
Perfect.
You got to tell me.
You're not actually attracted
to Calculon, right?
And if you are, don't tell me. Are you?
Certainly not.
But just once I'd like to eat dinner
with a celebrity
who isn't bound and gagged.
Is that so much to ask?
Well, I think you dating
a Manbot is a disgrace
and I refuse to be involved.
And you have way too much lipstick on.
Are you kidding? I need more lipstick!
Much more.
Ooh, yeah, that's the stuff.
Men love it when you really glob it on.
- No, they don't!
- No way!
Uh, please. Every man wants a tramp.
No wonder you girls aren't married.
I tell you, men are so much
better at being women.
But what if he wants to...
I mean, if he tries to...
Uh, Barry White?
I'll just tell him
I need a commitment first.
That'll stick a potato in his tailpipe.
Good lord, man!
What kind of temporary woman are you?
Look, why don't all of you just back off?
Can't a girl enjoy herself
without being judged?
Oh, dear, her mood swings
are getting wilder.
She's becoming a slave to her emotions.
Just like all women.
Particularly you, Leela.
I'm worried about him, too, Professor.
Hey, ma'am, you sure can put it away.
You saved me a trip to the dump. Bam!
I'd appreciate it
if you didn't bam the young lady.
Well, I'd appreciate it if I did.
So I guess we're even.
You know, Coilette,
I've never before met a woman
as fascinating as I am.
You're such a sweet, soft Fembot,
yet you have this free spirit about you.
And there it is.
It's as if you understand
the male mind better than I.
I've never met anyone like you.
Oh, yes, you have.
Coilette, I'd like to spend
some quality time with you.
What? Uh-uh! Oh, no way.
Not going to happen.
What kind of girl do you think I am?
Have I mentioned that I own the world's
biggest and most elegant yacht?
She's a lady
Whoa, whoa, whoa, she's a lady
Ooh!
Talking about that little lady
And the lady is mine
She's a lady
Whoa, whoa, whoa, she's a lady...
Whoo! I'm a trophy girlfriend.
No kidding.
These gifts have been coming nonstop.
I think Calculon's falling for you.
Bah! Any day now he'll dump me
for a new wad of arm candy.
Then I can turn back into a guy
and hock all this stuff.
It's just a game.
Coilette, I can't stop thinking about you.
I can't sleep at night.
Although, as a robot,
I don't do that anyway.
But if I did, I couldn't because...
I love you so.
Oh, my darling.
Will you marry me?
Oh, Calculon, yes, I will!
Maybe she's right about the lipstick.
I'll miss you, buddy.
You've been like a brother,
and then a sister to me.
And now you're getting married.
I love you, man.
The marriage is a scam.
Cool. What's for dinner?
What do you mean, a scam?
I marry Calculon, divorce him,
take half his money
and turn back into a guy.
It's sort of a two-person pyramid scheme.
That's marriage, all right.
That is so unbelievably manipulative.
Come on. You never went
on a date with a guy
just 'cause you were hungry?
Well, I...
Uh, I thought
I might like him on a full stomach.
Nice try, sister.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to meet with my wedding planner.
Zoidberg!
Zoidy-poo, please tell me
frilly is in this year.
I saw a frilly cake in here
you would remember all your life.
I know I will.
Late at night it taunts me
with its frosted beauty.
Order the cake, damn it!
I have something for you.
A remote control?
You got me a TV?
No, my dearest.
It's the remote control to my heart.
It symbolizes the power
you have to sway my emotions.
Will it work on my TV?
We don't need TVs.
We have each other.
Coilette, if I weren't able
to spend my life with you,
I would leap from this very balloon.
Come on with that.
Really?
Yes. We were meant to be!
So, you really and truly love me?
So much so that I'm prepared
to give up show business itself
to be with you.
But you always said
you'd rather burn down a convent
than give up show business.
I always said many things
but now all I want is a peaceful life
in a quiet villa overlooking a vineyard
with you.
Would we have donkeys?
All you could eat.
Oh, take me in your arms
and compress me!
Compress me tight!
Stop. Let us climb to the heavens
that the gods themselves might envy us.
I just don't think
I can go through with this scam.
So now you do want to marry him?
No. I just don't want
to hurt him or humiliate him.
Oh, curse this woman's heart!
Ick.
You're falling into the final
debilitating stages of womanhood.
You've waited too long
to switch back, you dingbat.
Okay, look, if I help you with this,
do you promise to get out
of my gender and stay out?
Uh-huh.
All right. Now, there's no way
to stop this marriage
without hurting Calculon,
but he's an actor.
If there's one kind of pain he can handle,
it's soap opera pain.
Okay, is everyone ready?
- Yep.
- Sure.
Basically.
Dearly beloved actors and casting people
who might be looking for someone
to play a preacher,
I welcome you.
The bride has written some vows
that we will now all pretend
to be interested in.
Dearest Calculon,
forever is not enough time
to tell you of the many ways I love you.
Is there a doctor in the...
I came as soon as I could.
Oh, it appears to be a case
of African Hydraulic Fever.
Dear God, the very illness
my TV character caught in Season 2
when I was holding out for more money.
It's often fatal.
Whatever happens, remember,
the flame of my eternal love
will burn forever.
Of course. But smoochy-pops,
I thought one could only catch
Hydraulic Fever
deep in the diamond mines of the Congo.
Coilette, you she-devil!
You really thought
you could steal those diamonds
from me and Congo Jack?
Those gems belong to the natives!
Hi-ya!
Oh, how cruel and melodramatic fate is.
Why?
Calculon, my darling,
your loud "why" brought me
partway back to life.
Congo Jack!
Another shocking twist!
Yes, I and have a message
for you from Colonel Mtumbe.
He says this is from Congo Jack.
Uh... Um...
No. No!
N-O-O-O!
I won't leave you.
Not until I'm sure
you understand the thing I said before
about my eternal love for you burning...
...et cetera.
I do.
Okay, then.
Mm. I'm a doctor. She's dead.
She lives no more.
But let us all find comfort
knowing that she truly loved me.
To honor my pain,
I shall star in a film
dedicated to her memory
and this time the Academy
will not deny me.
Not when they see
Coilette: A Calculon Story.
Coilette, your death fills me with sorrow,
anger, fear.
Every emotion an actor can display.
Turn off that crap-o-rama.
One mistake now, and Bender
will be trapped forever
between the already
ill-defined robot sexes.
Oh! Ooh! Ow! Ooh!
Well, Bender, I hope
this has taught you a lesson
about changing your sex
to win five gold medals.
It truly has.
My romance with Calculon
has shown me a lot about myself.
Almost done.
If only somehow, some way, he and I...
...could drive to Vegas,
pick up some floozy-bots
and void their warranties
all night long! Whoo!
Yay, my buddy's home.
And his respect for women
is back to normal.
I kind of hoped
this whole experience
would have left you a little more open
to your sensitive side.
Yeah, you'd think, but what ya gonna do?
Coilette, the skies themselves
weep upon the sweetest flower
of all the field.
- Ew!
- Gross!
Sentimental drivel poop.
Come on, Bender, let's go.
This chick flick is getting me all barfy.
Yeah, emotions are dumb
and should be hated.
Good night, forever, my turtle dove.
Good night, Calculon.
What did you say?
I said you two don't dress trampy enough.
I still got it.